How is she?
她情况如何？
In and out of the morphine drip.
因为注射吗啡半昏迷中
They got her stabilized is all I know.
我只知道他们让她稳定下来了
进去吧
Go on in.
不要‥
No.
Unfreeze your ass off that wall, then.
别只是靠着墙
Either pay your respects or get your head back into this case.
进去探视或回去办案
- Fuck this case. - Fuck it?
去他的案子
去他的？
You're just gonna call off your little crusade?
你要取消你发起的圣战？
Is that what you think it was? A crusade?
原来你这么想啊？
Avon Barksdale was a way
抓亚文巴斯戴尔是为了 炫耀自己聪明
to show everyone how smart I was
and how fucked up
并突显警局无能
the department is, that's all.
Just put Jimmy McNulty
把吉米麦诺提扛在肩上 来个游行表扬
up on your shoulders,
march him round the room,
break out the keg.
开啤酒庆祝好了
It was never about Avon Barksdale, Lieutenant.
根本不是为了抓亚文巴斯戴尔
It was all about me.
一切都只是为了我自己
你以为我不知道吗？
You think I didn't know that?
You think we all didn't know?
你以为我们都不知道吗？
Listen. This case is gonna move forward with you or without you.
听好 不管有没有你 这案子都会继续进行
This case got her shot.
这案子害她被枪击
I put a battery up her ass
我一直鼓动她 让她认为这案子有意义
and got her thinking it meant something.
And you know what?
结果呢？ 布瑞尔和罗斯都说对了
Burrell, Rawls, and them, they were right.
这根本是个烂案子
This case means exactly shit.
Well, I know it meant damn near nothing to me when you came in beating the drum.
当初你鼓动我 我也是这么想
But now we got that woman in there, that good police,
但现在那位优秀的女警察 必须靠插管维生
breathing through a fucking tube because it meant something to her.
因为这案子对她有意义
And the shooters who dropped Kima? They're still in the wind.
射伤金玛的枪手仍逍遥法外
And whoever sent those motherfuckers into that alley, he needs to get got, too.
我们也要把幕后主使抓起来
你可以站着那里喝酒自怜
You can stand there dripping with liquor smell and self-pity if you got a mind to,
but this case, it means something. Now.
但这案子 现在有了意义
If you walk through the garden
You better watch your back
Well, I beg your pardon
Walk the straight and narrow track
If you walk with Jesus
He'll save your soul
You gotta keep the devil
Down in the hole
All the angels sing
About Jesus' mighty sword
And they shield you with their wings
Keep you close to the Lord
Don't pay heed to temptation
For his hands are so cold
You gotta keep the devil
Way down in the hole
”这里才是我的家 华莱士”
You hit them again?
你又呼叫他了吗？
I been calling all morning.
我整个上午都在呼叫他 他还没回电话
They ain't hit me back yet.
Damn, we gonna tap out by noon.
该死 我们中午要缺货了
Yo, Poot! What we got over there?
阿普 还有多少？
两百管吧
200, maybe.
Shit.
可恶
What the fuck is this?
这是什么？
What the fuck you think, nigger? Fish food.
你想是什么？ 鱼饲料
还给我
Give me my shit.
Heads up.
大家注意
String.
线哥
I need your pagers. All y'all, the whole crew.
我要你们的呼叫机
所有人的
- Who else? - Sterling, Cass and Manny.
还有谁？
－史特林 小卡 曼尼 －你去拿过来
- Go get them shits. - How am I gonna talk to my girl?
我要怎么找马子？
Talk to your hand. That's the only girl you got.
马子就你右手啊 还用找
No more. Get out of here. Just get the fuck out of here, man.
没事了 走开
走开 老弟
No more pagers. Touts, lookouts, off the air, all right?
不用呼叫机了 跑腿和把风的都不用呼叫机
Nobody gonna use these cellphones except for you and Bodie,
除了你和波第 不准别人用这些手机
and y'all don't say shit on these, you understand?
你们也不准用手机 谈正事 懂吗？
We the only niggers that need them numbers.
只有我们需要知道号码
不准告诉老妈 马子 任何人 了吗？
Not your moms, not your girl, nobody. You feel me?
You use these phones to set up a meet, go to that meet and talk face to face, period.
只用电话来约定会面
见面后当面讲事情 没有例外
- So no more payphones? - You deaf? I said no phones.
－不再用公共电话？ －你聋了吗？
我说不用电话
How I'm gonna reach y'all?
我要怎么找你们？
All right, top number's for re-ups,
第一个号码是补货 第二个号码是求救
second number's for muscle.
You need me, hit me on the third number.
要找我打第三个号码
Learn them shits, then throw that shit away.
背下号码 丢掉那张纸
You doing this in the towers, too?
－大楼也是这样吗？ －所有地方都一样
Doing it everywhere. Payphones is dead.
呼叫机和公共电话全部停用
All right?
－了吗？ －了了
Yeah.
Yo, String. We need some re-up, man.
线哥‥
我们需要补货 中午就要缺货了
Re-up from where? You niggers ain't heard? Narcos took the main stash.
从哪里补货？ 你们没有听说吗？
条子抄了主藏货屋 不然我们干吗改变作法？
Why the fuck you think we changing up?
Back the fuck up, young'un. These shits ain't for you.
走开 小鬼 你不能看
All right.
Cool. There you go.
可以了
There we go. All right.
The gift of corrected vision.
视力矫正 市警局的礼物
Compliments of the BPD.
Dang, y'all are focused.
你们都好清楚
What man wouldn't be?
所有男人都会注意你
Excuse me.
失陪了
”服务中断”
They been cleaning us for a few days.
他们前几天在清理活动
- Last night they burned us all the way. - I knew it. I fucking knew it.
昨晚全部都断线了
我就知道‥ 他们果然料到了
- I'm in this motherfucker's head. - Not a message since early morning.
早上就没有讯息了
I had to cut Prez loose.
我甚至必须派普比出去 叫他去安纳波里斯
- Send him down to Annapolis. - For what?
－干什么？ －查本州竞选财务报告
State finance reports. I checked the stuff here but Barksdale's money has legs.
我查了本市竞选财务报告 但我觉得巴斯戴尔的钱长了脚
Shit. All the work we did to get up on this fucking wire.
可恶 我们为监听花了这么多心力
You don't hit these guys and expect them to stay in the pocket.
我们这样突击他们 他们当然会改变作法
- They know they dropped a police. - We need to change up, too.
况且他们知道自己杀了警察
那么我们也需改变做法
来吧
Come on. Shardene. Honey, this is Detective McNulty who's working with us.
夏汀 这位是麦诺提警官 我们一起工作
She works at Orlando's, helping us out there from time to time.
她在奥兰多俱乐部工作 不时会帮助我们
And now I think that she can see well enough to match faces to voices.
现在她的视力够好了 可把声音配上脸孔‥
Look, I'm not gonna lie to you. I'm scared of this shit.
莱斯特 我不要骗你 我非常害怕这件事
Time comes, though, I know you gonna step up.
但我知道时候一到 你就会挺身而出
We need Pearlman to approve her wearing a wire.
我们需要波曼核准她带麦克风
- Can I get a coffee? - How do you take it?
我可以喝杯咖啡吗？
－你要加什么？ －我来拿
I'll get it. A little cream, right?
不加奶精 对不对？
Those narco motherfuckers cleaned my shit out.
条子搜光了我的货
You can replace product and currency.
货和钱都能替补的
He right.
他说得对 要专注在真实的问题上
- We gotta focus on what's real here. - All of this shit is real. All of it.
这一切都是真实的
They wanna put me in a box.
他们想要送我去坐牢
I think what's important is to take stock.
我想重要的是检视一下
Ask yourself what's out there that can hurt you.
问自己 还有什么能伤害你？
你的弱点在哪里？ 需要清理什么地方？
Where are you weak? Where you need to clean up?
Think it through.
想一想 先从奥兰多开始
Start with Orlando, if Orlando rolled.
奥兰多如果招供了 至少会谈到俱乐部
You know he talked about the club, at least.
That punk-ass nigger ain't talk about shit else.
那个混蛋只会谈俱乐部 他只知道那么多
That's all he knew about. He wasn't with us.
他没有参与我们的生意 一直是圈外人
We kept him on the outside.
So you walk away from the club.
好 你与俱乐部无关
You're not on the license, you're not a listed owner.
执照不是你的 你不是拥有人
- They can't make a connect. - When did this shit start up?
他们无法牵连到你
倒楣事何时开始发生？
About the time that your nephew beat that charge.
大约在你外甥打赢官司时
When they found that witness with the lead in his dome, the shit hit the newspapers.
后来也许他们发现证人脑袋中弹
事情上了报
But around that time, the cops was on our shit.
那时候条子已盯上我们
The security guard whose testimony sprung D'Angelo.
那个警卫的证词 让迪安吉洛胜诉
- Nakeisha Lyles? - Bug-eyed ass bitch. But we hooked that up.
娜凯莎莱尔
小眼珠的臭婆娘 但我们让她翻了供
- So she can still hurt you, right? - Yeah.
－她仍能伤害你吧？ －对
The point is anybody who can hurt you can be put into play.
任何能伤害你的人 都会被警察利用
- The less I hear, the better. - All right, yo.
－我听到越少越好 －好吧
Hey, yo, lock that door.
锁上门好吗？
Lock that door.
锁上门
So we got Bird and Bey.
我们有小鸟和阿贝
Bird will stand tall.
小鸟不会屈服
他已经去坐牢 阿贝也要离开了
He already in jail, and Bey about to go, too.
And Wee-Bey hard like a rock.
威贝很牢靠
And we got Savino.
还有沙维诺
It ain't nothing but an Arm & Hammer charge.
沙维诺知道他只有假毒品罪名
He ain't gonna flip out over a motherfucking three years.
他不会为了三年而招供
没错
True.
Then we got that shit with Orlando, and the only problem there was Little Man.
那么奥兰多这件事 唯一的问题是小个子
Was.
曾经是‥
－曾经是 －对
- Was. - Was.
Who else?
还有谁？
It's over, your wire's cold.
结束了 停止监听
The court orders give me a total of 90 days on five phones.
法院总共给我９０天 监听五具电话
I'm doing the full 90.
我要用满９０天
你要监听故障的公共电话 尽管去吧
You want to sit listening to a bunch of broke-ass pay phones, have at it.
But you don't need all that manpower to do it.
但你不需要那么多人
You want some bodies back, I'll send a couple.
你想要一些人回去 没问题
Hold on, Lieutenant. I gave you those people.
慢着 分队长
人是我给你的 由我决定哪些人回来
I decide who comes back.
But feel free to speak your mind, if it were up to you.
但你可以表达想法 就假装由你来决定
He asked you a question, Lieutenant.
他问了你问题 分队长
I have no opinion. Take your pick.
我没有意见 随你挑
What's the name of that old detective from Pawnshop?
那个当铺组的老警官叫什么？
And that young one, Valchek's braindead son-in-law.
还有瓦柴克那个没用的女婿？
Freamon, Pryzbylewski.
费蒙 普比路斯基
Keep them.
留着他们
Send back Sydnor and Santangelo.
送回席诺与桑坦吉诺
And, Lieutenant, if you want to do anything
还有 分队长‥
你若想做 监听故障电话以外的事情
beyond listening to those dead phones,
you need to brief me first. Hmm?
你需要先向我报告
You did good, Cedric.
你的表现不错 赛卓
You play your cards right, all the work you did over the past few months
你的出手都很正确 这几个月成绩斐然
will speak volumes for you.
Major Spurgeon says he's retiring at the end of November.
史波金组长说 他１１月底要退休
- Opening up the Northwest Command. - That's right.
－西北区领导就有空缺了 －没错
Hi, Ronnie. Come in. Sit.
汪达请进 坐下吧
- Sheila, send Patrick in. - Yes, sir.
－席拉 请派崔克进来 －好的
- Anything up? - With me?
－有什么新案子？ －我吗？
Same shit, different file.
同样的东西 不同的档案
- How about the Barksdale thing? - You got my office reports.
－巴斯戴尔案呢？ －你收到我的报告吧？
We're looking into a bug in the man's nightclub.
监听停止了 但是想在他的俱乐部装窃听器
Aside from that, you're doing what?
除此之外‥
Pulling campaign finance reports for every politician in the city of Baltimore, right?
你也调查了本市 所有政治人物的竞选财务报告
我有吗 我们有吗？
I am?
We are?
And making calls to some contributors,
也打电话给一些捐款者 问问题 查背景
asking questions, doing background checks.
I don't know anything about this.
我一无所悉‥
I mean, Ronnie, where the fuck is all this going?
这是要查什么？
Those are public reports, right? I mean...
那些都是公开报告 不是吗？
No one on that detail has come to me for any kind of subpoena.
专案小组没人向我申请传票
You got back-doored, too, huh? Well...
你也被隐瞒了吗？
Just so there's no misunderstanding, I want to give you this.
为了不造成误会 我要把这份资料交给你
Copies of checks on the account of my re-election committee
我竞选委员会的 帐目支票影本
representing the return of five separate contributions, totaling $4,500.
退回了五笔捐款 总共４５００元
Also copies of the checks from the donor are represented in there, too.
还有捐款者的支票影本
Kind of like Caesar's wife and all that shit.
以避免瓜田李下之嫌
The only thing that we could come up with were those five checks.
我们只能找到那五张支票
I don't know those people, and I don't know why they gave.
我不知道那些人是谁 也不知道他们为何捐款
That money's gonna be returned to the donors.
那笔钱会立刻退还给捐款者
Guys, listen to me.
各位 请听我说
I don't know a fucking thing about anyone looking at campaign contributions.
我根本不知道有人在查 选举献金的事情
Be that as it may, this should make it clear that our hands are clean.
就算如此 这些文件可证明我们是清白的
汪达 我要你把文件交给 正在调查的人
I want you to take that back to whoever's on the hunt
and I want you to tell them they've got no quarrel with me.
我要你告诉他们 他们和我没有任何过节
What's up, String?
线哥‥
So y'all want to get with me?
你们找我？
We need to holler at your boy. You know, the one that dimed on Omar's bitch.
我们要找你的一个手下
那个通报欧玛爱人的小鬼 我想不起他的名字‥
Can't recall his name.
Which one?
哪一个？
The one that was at the Greek's that night.
那个在希腊店的小鬼 我们后来给他一笔赏金
- We paid him for the lookout. - What y'all need him for?
你们找他干什么？
What's it to you?
干你什么事？
－你们不用担心他 －什么？
- You ain't got to worry about him. - Say what?
- He's gone, he's out the game. - Out the game?
他走了 退出生意了
退出生意？
The man asked you a simple question.
他问你很简单的问题
I don't mean y'all no disrespect. You know I don't.
我没有不敬之意
你们了解我的 我要说的是那小鬼退出了
I am sitting here telling you that the boy is out the game.
Even if he wasn't out the game, he wouldn't be no problem.
就算他没退出 他也不是问题
Well, you know we just want to talk to him, D.
我们只是想找他谈谈 阿迪
Avon...
亚文‥
let the boy be.
放那孩子一马吧
Just let him be.
放他一马吧
Honey, just leave the damn thing alone.
亲爱的 别弄它了
- Where'd you get these, man? - Prevas.
－这是哪里买的？ －普马那里
Broadway market?
－大道市场？ －全市最棒的辣热狗
- Best chili dogs in the city. - No, man, not even.
差得远了
I'll give you ten bucks if you can name a better dog.
你说得出更棒的 我给你十块
- George's on Light Street. - The Greek joint?
莱特街的乔治午餐店
那家希腊店？ 你还在吃奶时就关门了
That closed when you were still sucking on your mama's nipples.
My mama's nipples? I was sucking on them last night.
我吃你妈的奶啦 你欠我十块
You owe me ten.
我是说现在最棒的热狗 古早时候不算
I said name a better dog you can have today, not in history.
You go get that dog right now.
－你只说最棒的热狗‥ －你现在就去买来
－你说最棒的热狗‥ －要买得到‥
- You cannot go get that now. - You said the best fucking dog.
你们这些小鬼给我安静 我什么都听不到
Can you please keep it down?
I can't hear a goddamn thing!
宝贝 你怎么这么丰满？
You'd know how much I got if you laid something on me.
你给我好东西 就会知道
- You like that freeze? - If you holding.
－你一定喜欢白粉吧？ －你有的话
I'm fixing to be. That's why I'm here, you know?
我来这里就是为了白粉
讨论一批货
'To discuss some things.'
When you done discussing, you come back.
你讨论完再来找我
All right, then. Hold that pose right there, shorty.
进来吧
别走开 妹子 待会给你一些好货
I'm gonna hook you up with some uncut.
Y'all niggers talk too damn much, man.
你们说太多了
她是谁 国宅警察吗？
Who the fuck is she? Housing police?
No, she's one of them civilians they got doing security.
不是 她只是警卫
- Housing cops wear the grey uniforms. - So she's not armed or nothing.
国宅警察穿灰色制服
－所以她身上没武器？ －看起来有吗？
Do she look it?
You leaving early?
－你要提早走？ －我提早上班 做午餐那一场
I was early, I worked the lunch crowd.
She's out.
她出来了
Anything?
听到什么了吗？
零碎的东西
Scraps. What we want is in that office.
我们要听办公室内的对话 可是夏汀没有好理由进去
There's no reason for Shardene to be in there long enough for us to get it.
－拿下来 我做不下去了 －你也不需要
- Take it out, I can't do this any more. - You won't have to.
I think they'll look at me and know. I need to quit.
他们好像一看我就会发觉 我要辞职
I don't need you wearing this wire, all right, honey?
你不用再戴窃听器了
I just need you to go in there and do one more thing.
只需要你再做一件事
Oh, look at this country nigger.
你看这个乡巴佬
- Damn, Wallace. - Wally!
－看是谁啊 华莱士 －华莱士
He kept crying till I sent him bus money.
他一直哭着要我寄巴士钱
All right. I just got tired of that same old country scenery.
我只是受不了 乡下一成不变的风景 太慢了
It was just too slow for me.
But did you get some of that country ass?
你有没有搞上乡下姑娘？
If he did, it was on four legs.
还是搞上了什么家畜？
Nigger, they got no farms down there, man. They did have some Bamas though.
那里没有农场
但周六晚上 百货公司有乐团演奏
They got their Saturday night shit down at Sears.
- They was like... - You were about to cry. You got DieHards?
－看了真是‥ －欲哭无泪吧？
你在那儿买了踢不烂鞋子吗？
- These Timbs. - Yeah, they Timbs.
－这是天柏蓝 －对 我看到了商标
I can see the tree on the side of them.
So you gonna put me back on the money?
可以让我回来管钱吗？
Hold. Look, if we do put you back on, you have to start as lookout, man.
我们让你回来 你要从把风开始
You lost your spot when you bucked town, dawg.
你离开时就放弃位置了
A real man would stay with his people.
真正的兄弟会留下来 不会看到血就想溜
He wouldn't run at the first sight of blood.
Y'all can still holler Five-0, right?
但你可以去把风 对吧？
If he want back on the money,
他若想管钱 就让他管钱
he back on the money. If he want it.
他真的想的话
My man might be thinking of going back
他也许想回学校 如我们谈过的 对不对？
to Edmondson like we talked about, right?
Come on, nigger, let's walk.
我们谈谈
－你没搞上动物吧？ －回头聊 阿普
Dawg, you ain't cornholed no animal for real, did you?
- Go ahead, Poot. - You're stupid.
Don't be fucking with my Sean John.
可别搞上邻居的狗啊
- So who caught it? - Garvey.
谁的案子？
卡维 他知道她是证人
He knows about the witness angle
but he doesn't want to run it up until he knows more.
但他要了解更多案情后 才告诉上司
Why ace Nakeisha Lyles now?
为何现在要干掉娜凯莎莱尔？
Now they know we're for real.
因为现在他们知道 我们是来真的
Avon's cleaning the house all the way.
亚文在彻底清理门户
First the phones go dead and then anyone he thinks we might be able to flip.
先断了电话 然后干掉 所有可能招供的人
What about the boy?
那个孩子呢？
该死的
Fuck me.
We took him to the shore Friday.
我们周五带他去海边奶奶家
The plan was to bring him back up for the Grand Jury.
本来计划周一带他回来 到大陪审团前作证
- What happened? - Greggs got shot.
－后来怎么了？ －葛芮遭到枪击
Trooper Reese?
瑞斯巡警 我是巴尔的摩 市警局丹尼尔分队长
This is Lieutenant Daniels, Baltimore Department.
Can someone go near Cambridge and check on a kid we got stashed down there?
能不能派人到剑桥附近 找一个我们安置的小鬼？
- 'Call him.' - There's no phone.
－你怎么不打电话？ －他住的地方没电话
- 'Can you hang on?' - I'll hold.
－请稍等 －好
叫席诺调一辆警车
Have Sydnor pull a car from motor pool.
We get the kid here. He sleeps on my sofa and we Grand-Jury him in the morning.
我们今晚把孩子载回来 睡在我家
明早就去作证
- What about your stripper? - The woman's got heart.
－你的脱衣舞女呢？ －她很有心
I mean, I want her protected. No more bodies, hear?
我要保护她 别再死人了
I got room at my place, she can lay up with me.
我家有房间 她可以住我那里 没问题
- I got no problem with that. - Remember who you are, Detective.
别忘了你的身份 警官
Protect and serve, Lieutenant. Protect and serve.
保护与服务人民 分队长
保护与服务
I'm saying, this here game, it ain't gonna work for you no more, man.
我是说这里对你不再有好处
你跑掉了 引起一些风波 虽然不是你的错
You leaving, you stirred up some shit.
- I'm saying it ain't your fault. - D, look.
阿迪 我了解你想说什么 但我在这里长大的
I appreciate what you trying to say and all, but I grew up in the courts, all right?
I been with them niggers since forever.
我从小就跟他们在一起
I guess this is home, right?
这里是我的家
You ain't hearing me, Wallace.
你没有听进去 华莱士
You ain't hearing me.
Anybody asks you whether you in this game, you tell them you in it for life, all right?
若有人问你是否还干这一行 你就说永远忠贞不二
Play it hard, play it tight and make sure niggers know you stand by your people.
你要表现得很强硬 让大家知道你不会屈服
No loose talk, no second thoughts, and no snitching.
不说闲话 不反悔 不告密
Play it like that.
要这样才行
Hey.
- What you doing down in the PJs? Lost? - I'm looking for you.
－你怎么来国宅 迷路吗？ －我来看你
You know I be down here working.
－你知道我在工作 －工作也要吃饭吧？
A working man got to eat.
- My favorite spicy fish cakes? - On the saltines with the mustard.
－我最喜欢的辣鱼饼？ －咸味加芥末
You gonna make me cry, you know.
我感动得快哭了
I need to get up out of here and get back to it.
我要回去工作了
- You be safe. - You, too.
－保重 －你也是
All right.
This here.
Sterling's, baby, we're about to feast.
史特林鱼饼 我们可以大吃一顿了
What the hell is Sterling's?
什么史特林？
Sterling's on 29th Street? Don't you know nothing?
２９街的史特林店 你不知道？
Shit, if it ain't up on the Westside, I don't know shit.
不在西区 我就不知道
Cos this shit, this is me, yo, right here.
这里才是我的家
Who was that, your new girl or something?
她是谁 你的新女友？
No, nigger, that's my mom.
才不是 她是我妈
You know Senator Davis?
你认识戴维斯参议员吗？
No, sir.
不认识
Lieutenant.
分队长
Clay wanted to meet you, see if there was any help he can offer.
克莱想见你 看看他能否提供协助
Help?
协助？
Your people are apparently pulling finance reports
你的手下在调阅财务报告 检查一些捐款者
and checking up on some of the contributors.
I wanted to reassure you on that front.
我想对你说明一下
我没有涉及贩毒 分队长
I'm not involved in drugs, Lieutenant.
很好
Good.
And this business with the senator's driver.
还有参议员司机那一档事‥
- Mr. Price, Damien. - Day-Day.
戴米安普莱斯先生
戴戴？
This er... This business with Mr. Price, this is a misunderstanding
普莱斯先生这件事是场误会
that is really of no concern to the police.
其实不需要劳动警方
我们在他身上找到二万现金
We hid $20,000 of cash on him
delivered out of a project tower by a known drug suspect.
从知名毒贩的国宅大楼送出
The money was banded and manicured by denomination.
钞票都照面额整理成捆
This is...
这件事‥没有犯罪
There's no crime here.
That was money that Damien already had on him when he drove to Franklin Terrace.
戴米安开车去大楼前 就已经拿着那笔钱
Money from a cash-bar fundraiser the previous weekend.
是前一周的募款现金
We filed an amended finance report that shows that...
我们申报了修正过的财务报表‥
Fine.
很好
There's no probable cause for a search of Mr. Price.
搜索普莱斯先生并无合理事由 这点我们都同意
I think we are in agreement on that.
No, there was PC for the search.
不对 有合理事由的
You're saying you have evidence that a senatorial aide is involved in drugs?
你有证据显示议员助理贩毒？
I'm saying we had reason to stop Mr. Price and search him,
我是说 我们有理由 拦下普莱斯先生进行搜身
after which we discovered $20,000 in cash, in banded, manicured bills.
后来我们发现二万元现金
That's all I'm saying.
我只是这个意思
Explain to this motherfucker just what it is he's doing here.
欧文 请你跟这混蛋 解释一下好不好
- Lieutenant Daniels? - Excuse me, sir.
－丹尼尔分队长‥ －对不起 长官
But it's pretty basic.
这一切都非常简单
If the senator is not involved in anything illegal then he doesn't need to worry.
参议员若无涉及不法 他就不需要担心
I can't be any clearer about it than that.
我说得再清楚不过了
Fool, what do you think?
笨蛋 你是怎么想的？
That we know anything about who gives money?
我们会知道捐款者的身份吗？
That we give a damn about who they are or what they want?
我们会在意他们的意图吗？
We have no way of running down them or their stories.
我们无法调查他们的背景 我们也不在乎
We don't care. We just cash the damn checks, count the votes, and move on.
我们只是兑现支票 计算选票 继续做我们的事
Anything else, Deputy Burrell?
还有事吗 布瑞尔副局长？
Gentlemen.
告辞了
You need to put his ass on a foot post so far out in the sticks
你应该派他到森林当巡警 跟费城警察当邻居
that he's gonna see the Philadelphia cops walking towards him.
Now you just ain't talking to me now, Erv.
你面对的不只是我 欧文
You talking to the Mayor, the city caucus, the state central committee.
你还要面对市长 市党部 州中央委员会
你的手伸进我们口袋了
And right now, you got your hand in our pocket.
18, baby!
第十八名 宝贝
第‥十‥八‥
Eight-eight-eight-eight-eight-eight-eight- eight-eight-eight-eight-eight-eight.
18 with a bullet, baby.
第十八名
Detective Sergeant Hauk reporting for duty, sir.
贺格小队长报到 长官
And the best part? Carver's 37.
最棒的是卡佛才３７名
You know, it helps if you know them by the numbers.
他说知道号码比较有帮助 听起来更专业
It makes you sound more professional.
Fucking Carver. He gets back from training, he's gonna kiss the stripes.
等卡佛受训回来 他得亲我的官阶
I'm gonna make him kiss the stripes.
- Congratulations. - Thank you, sir. Appreciate it.
－恭喜 －谢谢长官
贺格小队长
- Sergeant Hauk? - God help us.
老天保佑我们
- Daniels. - 'Daniels, this is Trooper Reese.
我是丹尼尔
我是瑞斯巡警 孩子的奶奶说他已经走了两天
'Grandmother says this kid's been gone two days.'
Wallace is out of pocket. Two days.
华莱士溜走两天了
Thanks.
谢谢
Ain't no re-up in the towers, neither?
大楼也没补货？
No. Shop dead, yo.
没有 店关门了
- What up, man? - Same old, same old.
－混得好吗？ －老样子
What's up with that boy?
那孩子是怎么回事？
Oh, man. He just a punk, that's all.
他只是个混混
D put him back on count though.
－阿迪又让他管钱了 －真的？
Word? I heard he was out the game.
我听说他退出了
He was, but he back now.
本来是 但是他回来了
Where he been at?
他去哪里了？
Down his granny house, he says.
他说去奶奶家
奶奶家是吧‥
His granny.
I heard he damn near shit his pants when
听说他看到欧玛爱人的死状 差点尿湿裤子
he saw what happened to Omar's bitch.
He just ain't built for this, you know. His heart pump Kool-Aid.
他不适合这一行 心太软了
Right. What about you?
你呢 你适合吗？
You built for this shit?
No doubt.
没问题
You ready to put the work in?
你准备做事了吗？
You got heat?
你有枪吗？
All right, soldier.
好了 战士
It's clear upstairs.
楼上没人
- No extension cords. No juice boxes. - No Wallace.
－没有延长线 没电 －华莱士也不在
老包的餐盒都不送纸巾
Dang, boy, Chink Bob's never be putting no napkins in the bag.
Motherfucker. Napkins expensive and shit.
－因为纸巾很贵 －我的钱也很贵
So is my money.
All right, come on, go. Something to eat?
孩子们 来吃东西
Y'all know what's here.
吃的来了
Y'all need to get up in this Chinese food cos I'm looking needy right about now.
我们来吃中国菜 我好饿
What you listening to? Hold up, take them plates first.
你在听什么？ 等一下 先拿盘子
Big Tymers, their new video on 106th and Park.
大提摩 他们在公园路 拍新的音乐录影带
－公园路？ －这个乐团很正
- 106th and Park? - The joint is vicious.
很正？
－现在你叫什么绰号？ －巴夫 因为我有料
- What they call you? - Buff, cos I got the stuff.
You got the stuff? You need to get up in these egg rolls or something.
你有料？ 你要吃点蛋卷了
Any word on the kid?
有没有小鬼的消息？
I rolled around Cambridge all night with his B of I.
我在剑桥拿照片问了一整晚
If he's down there, he ain't got no profile.
就算他在剑桥 也没有纪录可查
We got lookouts to every car.
我们在西区和中区监视车辆 想查出他母亲的地址
We're trying for an address on his mother.
- Detective. - Lieutenant.
－警官 －分队长
Wire's dead so we've been ordered to begin sending bodies home.
监听结束了 我们奉命让你们一些人归队
Sydnor, we have a little longer because Cantrell still owes me.
席诺还可多待一段时间 因为肯特罗还欠我人情
- You OK with Rawls? - I gave him his clearance, right?
你跟罗斯还好吧？
我为他破了案 他还要怎么样？
What's he gonna do to me?
Keep it warm, Sanny.
跟他保持友善 小桑
What's that?
那是什么？
- Plans for Orlando's. The upper floors. - This is the property next door.
奥兰多俱乐部的二楼平面图
－这是隔壁的屋子 －你怎么这么快就找到？
- How'd you get them so quick? - CoStar.
网路搜寻
Plan is to get a remote mike into the office. Maybe even some fiber optics.
计划是在办公室装麦克风 甚至光纤摄影机
Only we don't know where Avon's office is.
但我们还不知道 亚文的办公室位置
Which is where Shardene helps us out.
这就是夏汀要帮我们的地方
Is she gonna take out a tape and ask Avon to hold the other end?
她要拿尺去量？ 叫亚文帮她拉尺吗？
Ain't none of y'all been in the military?
你们都没当过兵？
How do you learn a 30-inch, quick-time?
如何快速丈量３０寸？
Draft-dodging peace freaks.
你们这些躲兵役的和平分子
－给我尺与绳子 －为何要我拿？
- Get me a ruler and some string. - Why me?
Why? Why?
为什么‥？
- Because the man said so, that's why. - Wallace ain't no snitch.
因为老大说的
－华莱士不是告密的 －你怎么知道？
Man, how you know? How you know where he been running to?
你怎么知道他跑到哪里？
他在吸毒 我看到了
He was getting high. I've seen him cop.
He probably went down to the shore to clean that shit up.
他也许去海边戒毒
Man, if he using, then you know he ain't reliable. Come on, think.
他要是吸毒 就不可靠 用用脑袋吧
老大下令了 我们不服从就滚蛋
Look, the man gave the word, all right? We either step up or we step the fuck off.
That's the game.
这一行就是这样‥
That's the fucking game.
赛卓
Cedric.
You ever hear of an elected official in Baltimore giving money back?
你听过巴尔的摩 当选的官员退还捐款吗？
Whatever you're doing scared my boss shitless.
不管你在查什么 我的上司吓坏了
He calls me in and hands me that.
竟然交给我那份文件
Forgive me for prying into the details of our investigation.
请原谅我察问调查细节
I know, it's annoying. But what the hell are you guys doing?
我知道这样很烦人 可是你们到底在干吗？
你看
这是亚文的钱吗？
Is that Avon's money?
Eastside addresses but maybe Barksdale has fronts we don't know about.
东区的地址 也许巴斯戴尔 还有我们不知道的门面
- State's Attorney's returning this? - Fast as he can.
州检察长退回这些钱？
仿佛烫手山芋 你们挖出一些脏东西
Y'all are stirring some shit here. Why didn't you tell me?
怎么不告诉我？
Aren't you better off that we didn't?
不讲不是比较好？
I remember my mom used to bring me here.
我记得我妈会带我来这里 我们会去一家叫梦幻水果的店
We used to go to Fruit Fantasy.
Orange soda, some shit like that?
喝柳橙可乐之类的玩意吗？
No, these were fresh.
不对 是新鲜的水果 但我妈会加酒进去
My mom poured Bacardi in hers though.
- Wasn't much she didn't pour it into. - Talking about her like you're still a kid.
她什么东西都加酒
你看你 像还没长大的小孩
I got to thinking on her.
我会想到她 你不用一直这么严厉
Your ass ain't got to be hard all the goddamn time.
软弱就会坏了大事
Soft link break the chain.
What are you, a boy or a man?
你是男孩还是男子汉？
我是男子汉
I'm a man.
So what are we gonna do, man, go have some fun?
现在要干吗 去找乐子吧？
OK, on this floor. It's the second room from the rear.
这层楼 后面算来第二个房间
The stairs start 30 paces from the front. There's 24 stairs, about a foot each.
楼梯从前面算来第３０步
２４层阶梯 每层约一尺
When you get to the top floor, it's eight paces to the door of the dressing room
来到楼上 化妆间的门是八步
and another 10 to the back room.
再走十步就是后面的房间
80 to 110 in from the front.
从前面算来８０到１１０
The third floor of this building is vacant.
这栋楼的三楼是空的
Otherwise we'd need a warrant.
不然我们就需要搜索票了
- $15. - Here take $10.
－１５块 －给你１０块
－１５块 －我没看到车表 滚啦
- $15. - Motherfucker, I don't see no meter.
Get the fuck out of here.
现在凌晨两点半
It's 2:30 in the morning.
Easy now. Hole only needs to be as big as your finger.
轻一点 洞只要手指一样大就好
Not those sausage fingers you got.
不是你那种粗手指
You know what big hands mean.
这才叫大手
你们知道什么是大手吧
You know what big hands mean, right?
Lieutenant, I just pulled a fresh address for Wallace's mother.
分队长 我刚查到 华莱士母亲的新地址
We're OK here.
有我们就行了
Where y'all at?
你们躲到哪里了？
All right, when I find y'all, y'all gonna get it.
等我找到你们就倒楣了 最好现在就出来
You better come out now.
Where y'all at?
泰勒 你们在哪里？
Look, I'm not even playing with y'all right about now.
不跟你们玩了 听到没有？
You hear me?
Game over. Where the fuck y'all at?
游戏结束 你们在哪儿？
When I find y'all, I'm beating your asses. Now where y'all at?
我找到你们就要打屁股 你们躲到哪里了？
Don't let me find y'all.
我来找你们了
Check this, Poot. Little Man left his player and shit.
阿普你看 小个子的随身听留在这里
Yo, man, you...
你是个软弱的家伙
You a weak-ass nigger, man.
You should've stayed down in the country, man.
你应该留在乡下
Y'all my niggers, yo.
我是你兄弟‥
这是你自找的
You fucking brought this on yourself.
- We boys! - You brought this on yourself.
－兄弟‥ －你自找的
Why it gotta be like this?
何必要这样子？
You my niggers from BC, remember that?
别忘了我们都是黑皮肤
Come on, wetting your fucking pants, like you a little boy.
你尿湿裤子了 像小孩一样 做个男子汉
Be a man! Stand up like a motherfucking man.
像男子汉一样站好
- Y'all my niggers. - You said you a fucking man. Stand up.
你说你是男子汉 站直
That's us, man.
我们是兄弟啊
Do it, goddamnit, if you...
你快开枪啊‥
Darcia Wallace? We're looking for your son.
达西亚华莱士？ 我们在找你的儿子
Thought you might know his whereabouts.
也许你知道他的下落
Where-a-who? Shit, I be looking for that smart little nigger, too. Boy took me for $10.
哪里 谁？
我也在找那小黑鬼 他偷了我十块钱
- Recently? - What's going on?
－最近吗？ －外面在搞什么？
Nothing.
没事
Couple of police interrupting me, while I'm trying to get my drink on.
两个警察打断我喝酒
- Your son might be in danger. - He will be if he shows up.
－你儿子可能有危险 －他回来才有危险
Snatched that $10 out my purse.
偷拿我十块 我会把他打得鼻青脸肿
- I'll slap the bright out his eyes. - Here's my card.
这是我的名片 见到他就通知我
You run into him, you call me.
”奥兰多绅士俱乐部”
- 'Y'all got a tape?' - 'Over there, man.'
－你们有卷尺吗？ －在那里
'All right, let's see what we got here.'
量量这个尺寸多大
He's packing shit up.
他在打包
'What you scratching your head for, man?
你抓什么头？
'How y'all get the safe in here, and you can't get it out?'
你们能把保险箱搬进来 却搬不出去？
打报案台 告诉接电话的人 不要说出你的名字
Just dial 911 and talk to whoever pick up.
Don't say your name or nothing.
Just say there's been an animal hurt inside the house and then you hang up.
说屋子里有只动物受伤 然后就挂断
'What up? So what do you need from me?'
怎么样 你找我吗？
'I need you to run up to NYC to pick up a little something.'
我要你去纽约市拿东西
'Look, I know we tapped and all.
我知道我们缺货了 大家都等着补货 但我没拿过
'Everybody waiting on the re-up, but I never made that run before.'
I feel like I don't have that many people around me I could really trust.
现在我觉得 身边没有让我真正信任的人
Not like I can kin. You follow me?
不是我不信任人 你懂吧？
- All right? - How much is it?
多少货？
We just need to maintain.
只要能维持下去 足够大楼用就好
Put out enough so we can keep hold of them towers.
- When? - Tonight.
－什么时候？ －今晚
好
All right.
- 'What am I driving?' - 'A rental, nothing flash.'
－我开什么车去？ －租来的
－租来的？ －福特金牛
'Where from?'
－哪里租来的？ －我不知道 就是车行‥
'I don't know where from, man, one of those places by the airport.'
- 'Yeah.' - We got something real.
－喂？ －我们听到了好情资
- 'I'm on my way.' - All right.
－我马上过去 －好
Shit!
该死
- Which one? - The rental there, the Taurus.
－哪一辆？ －租来的 福特金牛
I gotta say, Lieutenant, you got mad suction with the federales.
分队长 我得承认 你跟联邦调查局关系真不错
Yeah, Daniels.
我是丹尼尔
Yeah.
好
Where?
哪里？
Wallace?
华莱士？
”市中心重新开发案 获得二亿五千万经费”
Poor fucking kid.
可怜的孩子
With Wallace gone, that's Stringer out of the box.
华莱士死了 线哥就脱罪了
He was in there changing his fucking clothes.
他进去换衣服
You believe that?
你相信吗？
Boy had to get himself correct.
人总是要衣装
We're on. No need for an eyeball. Let the satellite do the work.
开始行动 不需要跟踪 用卫星就好
How about I call my lawyer, have him explain that whole profiling thing to you?
我要找律师 让他来说明我的纪录
先生
Mr. Barksdale, our tollbooth cameras have you on the GW Bridge at 23:10 hours,
收费站摄影机拍到你在 ２３点１０分上华盛顿大桥
then re-entering the turnpike at the same exit 35 minutes later.
３５分钟后回到同一个出口
Why did you drive all the way to New York for half an hour?
你为何开这么远的车到纽约 只停留半小时？
Step out of the car, sir. Keep your hands where I can see them.
请下车 举起双手
Turn around, face the car, hands on the roof.
转过身 把手放在车顶
- Are you carrying any weapons, sir? - No.
－有携带任何武器吗？ －没有
- Knives, any needles? - No.
刀子或针筒？ 我需要知道的违法药物？
Any illegal substances I should know about?
OK. Spread your legs back.
把腿张开 再张开一点
Spread your legs back more.
OK, slowly bring your right arm around your back.
慢慢把右手伸到背后
Now bring the other one.
另一只手
- Remember me? - Lawyer.
－记得我吗？ －律师
Easy. We're just getting started.
轻松点 我们才刚开始
- Lawyer, motherfucker. - OK, so you're hard, but guess what?
律师 混蛋
好吧 你很强悍 告诉你 我才不在乎
- I could give a fuck. - You? I'm tired of your games.
你？ 我受够你的游戏了
You want me to write a letter, or some shit like that?
你又要我写封信吗？
No game we need to run. You're popped with a kilo of uncut.
我们不用玩游戏 你被逮到持有一公斤海洛因
Not that you messed up. You did everything right.
你并未犯错 你很守规矩 没超速 灯号正确
Speed limit, turn signals, working tail-lights.
问题是 为何巡警会拦下你？
Question you gotta ask is how'd those troopers know to pull you over?
Someone else fucked up. You following me?
别人搞砸了
你懂吗？
But it's you they're gonna blame and you who's gonna do the jolt.
因为他们会怪你 你要去坐牢
- Lawyer. - That'd be Levy, right?
律师
李维吗？
He's getting paid by your uncle, is that right?
他是你舅舅请的吧？
他会照顾你的利益？
He's looking out for your interests.
More than you.
比你会
Listen.
听好
I ain't saying another damn thing
除了我的律师之外 我不会对任何人说话
to nobody but my lawyer.
Oh, by the way, your boy Wallace, shot dead in the low-rises.
对了 你的手下华莱士 在矮楼被枪杀了
That's how y'all take care of your own, right?
你们就是这样照顾自己人？
You're a lying motherfucker.
你在骗我
So what? You want me to write a letter to his mom, too?
你要我写信给他母亲吗？
Get the fuck out of here.
给我滚吧
You didn't have to send him the way you did.
你没必要派他去的
In one car? He should've been trailing a mule.
只有一辆车 他应该跟着一辆掩护车
95 or on the train, it don't make no difference. He shouldn't have been alone.
开车或坐火车都一样 他不该自己一个人去
- Look here, Brianna. - Ain't you ever heard of a trap-car?
－贝安娜‥ －你没听过陷阱车吗？
You send my son to New York in a motherfucking rental
你竟然派我儿子 开租用车去纽约？
and let him ride with that package in the trunk?
让他开车载货？
- I'm sorry. - That won't bring him out of prison.
－我很抱歉‥ －抱歉也无法让他不坐牢
Better make sure that Jew lawyer of yours earns his money, huh, eh?
你的犹太律师 最好拿出看家本领
迪安吉洛必须承担责任
- D'Angelo has to do his part. - Meaning what?
－什么意思？ －你喜欢你开的车吗？
You like the car you driving in, right?
喜欢这个房子吗？ 我给你的 你喜欢吗？
You like this crib? I put you in this crib. You like it?
We all got a lot to protect here. You need to remind him of that.
我们都有许多东西要保护 你要提醒他这一点
So when it come down to it, he can stand up tall.
面临压力时 他才能坚强并承受
You ain't gotta worry about my child.
你不用担心我儿子
I raised that boy, and I raised him right.
他是我养大的 我养得很好
It wasn't me who fucked up.
不是我搞砸的
Really? So who did? Why the fuck are we here?
是吗 不然是谁搞砸的？
All you need to do is keep your head through the bail hearing.
你只需要熬过保释听证会
- We've got a shot at bringing you home. - Then what? Huh?
我们很有机会带你回家
然后呢？
Who gonna take the weight for all the shit in the trunk of that car?
谁要为那些货顶罪？
Where's Wallace at?
华莱士呢？
Where's the boy, String?
那个孩子呢 线哥？
D'Angelo, shut your mouth.
迪安吉洛 闭上你的嘴
Where's Wallace?
我只想知道华莱士呢？
That's all I want to know.
Kid, you'd better think.
孩子 你最好想一想
Where the fuck is Wallace?
华莱士呢？
Huh, String? String?
线哥‥
Look at me. Look at me!
看着我‥华莱士呢？
Where the fuck is Wallace?
I don't want this motherfucker representing me.
我不要这个低级律师代表我
I'm gonna get my own man.
我要自己找律师
So just get back in your car
你回去车上 往南开回家吧
and get the fuck back down south.
All right, you stupid motherfucker. You made your decision.
你这个蠢蛋 这是你做的决定
对 我做的决定 华莱士呢 线哥？
I made my decision. Where's Wallace at?
Where the fuck is Wallace? Where's Wallace?
华莱士在哪里？
String! Where the fuck is Wallace?
线哥 华莱士在哪里？ 去你的
God damn!
Bring him in, you're done.
逮捕他 你就功成身退了
Why?
为什么？
We have the charge whenever we want it.
我们随时能起诉他
Why not stay up on the bug in his office?
为何不继续用 他办公室的针孔摄影机？
The bug you didn't brief me about.
你并没有告诉我那个摄影机
I thought your little bird told you everything we did a minute after we did it.
我还以为你的眼线 会向你通报一切
One of ours got hurt. That should mean something.
一名组员受伤了 这应该有所意义
We're hunting her shooters and by the grace of God and your good work,
我们在追查枪手
现在由于你的优良表现 我们可以起诉主要目标
we've got a viable case on our main target.
Just charge Barksdale with the attempt purchase from New York
起诉巴斯戴尔到纽约买毒 一切就可以收网了
and bring it all home.
What about Stringer? He slipped off the hook when we lost the boy.
他的副手线哥呢？ 少年证人被杀后 他就脱罪了
We've done all we can.
我们已经尽力了
Are you hearing me?
你没听清楚吗？ 这些人开枪射伤一名警察
These are the people responsible
for dropping a police.
Not just the shooters,
不只是枪手 还有幕后指使者
but ones who make the dirt happen.
我要让他们坐大牢 而不是什么短刑期
I'm trying to put them down for real,
not for some short-time bit.
That all you trying to do?
你只是想做这些吗？
If it is, how is it you have people pulling
既然如此 你们为何要调查 竞选财务报告？
campaign records and finance reports?
The fuck has that
那到底有什么关联？
got to do with anything?
The money is part of my case.
金钱也是我案子的一部分
I was willing to say otherwise,
之前我也许愿意 让你和你的朋友掩饰下去
to let your friends hide some of that dirt, but not now.
－但现在不行了 －你要谈掩饰？
You want to talk about dirt? Have at it.
尽管来吧
Talk about your Eastern district days.
我们来谈谈东区的日子
Talk about what was going on
谈谈你在药管组的疯狂日子
when you ran wild in the DEU.
That's just talk.
－那只是传闻 －只是传闻？
Just talk?
FBI field reports.
联邦调查局调查报告
You came into a lot of money, quick.
你以前很快就有大笔进帐
And you can go to jail just as quick if I start asking the right questions.
我若开始提出正确的问题 你很快就会坐牢
This case ends, or you are done.
这案子不结束 你就完了
Hell, I don't even need you to lock up Barksdale.
我甚至不需要你逮捕巴斯戴尔
I'll have your major debrief your detectives and type the warrants himself.
我会叫你的组长指挥你的手下 他自己来打拘票
This case is done.
这案子结束了
随你高兴怎么做
You do what you feel.
You wanna pull Avon in on half a case? You go ahead.
你要用半件案子来逮捕亚文 尽管去吧
You wanna put my shit in the street?
你要调查我的事情 欢迎
Feel free.
But the Eastern had a lot of stories.
但东区有很多故事 不只我一个
Mine ain't the only one.
A lot of people came through that district.
很多人来自东区
你想办我 早就办了
If you were gonna do me,
I'd already be done.
But there ain't nothing you fear more
但现在你最怕的 就是难看的头条新闻吧？
than a bad headline now, is there?
You'd rather live in shit
你宁愿住在粪坑 也不愿让人看到你清理
than let the world see you work a shovel.
You can order warrants, and I'll serve them.
你可以申请拘票 我会执行
But as long as I have days left
但只要监听时间还没用完 这案子就会继续进行
on those dead wires, this case goes on.
Yo, look at these Delta Force motherfuckers, man.
你看这些特种部队
- Look at them. - All right.
- What's up with Levy? - He said he gonna meet us down there.
－李维呢？ －他说会和我们在那里碰面
I still didn't get this safe out of here yet, man. How much money in it?
该死 我还没移出保险箱 里面有多少钱？
- $150,000. - $150,000.
１５万
－１５万？ －对
Open it up, man. No sense in ruining a good safe.
打开来 不用破坏一个好保险箱
This isn't as much fun as I thought it would be.
没有我想的那样好玩
特警队最喜欢打破东西
The SWAT love to break out their toys.
Do they think it's Tony Montana? They probably haven't touched a gun in years.
他们以为里面有军队吗？ 这些人可能多年没碰枪了
Fuck this shit.
真是的
You and me, Lieutenant.
你跟我去吧 分队长
What units are in the alley?
巷子是哪个小组？
Any sightline to the rear door?
后门有人监视吗？
谁在屋顶上？
10-4, who has the roof?
We're gonna move in on my command. Everyone stand by.
听我下令攻坚 所有人预备
We're not gonna need your men today.
今天我们不需要你们 叫他们撤回
- Now wait a minute. - My case. Back your men off.
－等一下‥ －我的案子 你们都后退
Catch you later.
之后再抓你 （之后再见）
”市中心重新开发案 获得二亿五千万联邦经费”
没问题吗？
好的
It's good.
Barksdale's wearing bracelets.
巴斯戴尔上了手铐
Still no Wee-Bey, no Little Man?
还没找到威贝和小个子？
No, nothing there.
还没有
”被捕”
This is the best work I ever did. I never did a case like this. But it's not enough.
这是我办过最棒的案子
我从没办过这样的案子
但这样还不够
I gotta go back to Auto tomorrow morning and...
明天我要回汽车窃盗组了
但却觉得事情还没有完结
- I just feel like this just ain't finished. - Detective.
警官‥
待续
谢谢观赏